unic.org.in 2017-05-01

# United Nations Information Centre for India and Bhutan

**Privacy Statement**

**Your privacy on the Internet is of utmost importance to UNIC India. As a general policy, UNIC India does not collect any personal information on its websites that identify you or any demographic information about you.**

This privacy statement describes UNIC India’s policy concerning the gathering and sharing of visitors’ information through the UNIC India web site. 

**_1\. What information does unic india collect?_**

In general, you can browse the UNIC India site without revealing any personal information about yourself. The only information we gather during general browsing is from standard server logs. These include your IP (Internet Protocol) address, domain name, browser type, operating system, and information such as the web site that referred you to us, the files you download, the pages you visit, and the dates/times of those visits.

**_2\. What does unic india do with this information?_**

The information gathered during general browsing of the “unic.org.in” domain is used to analyze trends and usage of the UNIC India site and to improve the usefulness of the site. It is not connected with any personal information.

**_3\. What about information security_**

We do not sell or share any personally identifiable information volunteered on the UNIC India site to any third party. Any information provided to UNIC India by users of the UNIC India site is held with the utmost care and security, and will not be used in ways other than as set forth in this privacy policy, or in any site-specific policies, or in ways to which you have explicitly consented. UNIC India employs a range of technologies and security measures to protect the information maintained on our systems from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

All our employees who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of official business matters, including personal data.

The UNIC India site contains links to sites external to the unic.org.in domain. UNIC India is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

**_4\. Our contact information_**

For questions or queries regarding this privacy policy, please contact the [webmaster](mailto:sharma@unicindia.org).

**_5\. Website usage agreement_**

Use of this Site constitutes agreement with the following terms and conditions.

The United Nations Information Centre for India and Bhutan (“UNIC India”) maintains this web site (the "Site") as a courtesy to those UNIC India may choose to access the Site ("Users"). The information presented herein is for informative purposes only. UNIC India is pleased to allow Users to visit the Site and download and copy the information, documents and materials (collectively, "Materials") from the Site for User's personal, non-commercial use, without any right to resell, create derivative works, subject to the terms and conditions outlined in the copyright notice, and also subject to more specific restrictions that may apply to specific material within this Site.
